你好,杰克船长。
Hello, Captain Jake.
这是你的猫在麦克风上，博士。爸爸，把你的腿抬起来。
This is your cat on the mic,Dr. Daddy-O - Put your leg up.
在节奏的综合播放一些旧的，一些新的，一些借来的和一些蓝色。
Moving right along on Rhythm Roundup playing some old, some new,some borrowed and some blue.
你爱我吗，宝贝?
Do you love me, baby, do you?
你的脚后跟跟在我后面，快点。
Hook your heels behind me there, come on.
这是另一个10美元。
That's another $10.
接下来，我从那个穿天鹅绒衣服的男人那里得到了一个性感的。
Coming up, I got a hot one from the man in velvet.
热,男人。
Hot, man.
把屁股抬高一点。
Get those buns up higher.
该死的，把你的手从我屁股上拿开。
Goddamn it, get your hand off my ass.
对不起。
Sorry.
好吧。
Okay.
像这样挤压它。
Squeeze it like that.
到这里来。
Come here.
把腿抬上去。-嗨。
Get those legs up there. - Hey.
吠，来吧，吠。
Bark, come on, bark.
树皮,来吧。
Bark, come on.
像狗一样吠叫。
Like a dog, bark.
吠，来吧，吠!
Bark, come on, bark!
树皮!
Bark!
嗨,克里斯。
Hey, Chris.
你最好在她的人来之前快点。
You better hurry up before her man gets here.
来了!
Coming!
等一下，伙计。
Wait a minute, man.
等一下。
Wait a minute.
你最好把排气管穿好。
You better get your exhaust pipe dressed.
他们在路上了，伙计。
They're on their way, man.
有多少?
How many?
三。
Just three.
——三个?——这是正确的。
- Three? - That's right.
你这个混蛋。
You son of a bitch.
放开我，该死的，放开我。
Let go of me, goddamn it, let go.
该死的你。
Goddamn you.
有人会回来睡觉吗?
Would somebody come on back to bed?
-你个混蛋-我的牛仔裤呢?
- You son of a bitch. - Where's my jeans?
我的鞋子在哪里?
Where's my shoes?
帮我找到我的鞋子，该死的。-给我拿杯喝的。
Help me find my shoes will you goddammit. - Get me a drink.
我说了，他们在路上了。-来吧，我叫你。
I told you,they're on their way. - Come on, I'll bark for you.
拜托，我的裤子呢?
Come on goddammit, where's my pants?
我找不到我的裤子了。
I can't find my pants.
我拿了钱包，来吧。
I got the purse, come on.
韦恩,帮帮我!
Wayne, help me!
操，你个狗娘养的!
Oh, shit, you son of a bitch!
嘿，你要去哪儿?
Hey, where are you going?
你混蛋。
You bastards.
该死的六块钱，那个婊子。
Six lousy goddamn dollars, that whore.
我以为我一个人就值那么多钱。
I thought I was worth that much alone.
看来你没拿到钱啊，兄弟。
Looks like you didn't get paid, brother.
来吧，克里斯，我们走。
Come on, Chris, let's go.
好吧，车在哪儿?
All right, where's the car?
它已经被拖走了。
It's been towed away.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
因为它不在这里，我能读。
Because it's not here and I can read.
哦,太好了。
Aw, that's great.
现在我们到底该怎么办?
Now what the hell are we gonna do?
好吧，我们去拿。
Well, we go get it.
在哪里?
Where?
他们把车拖到了那里。
To where they towed it.
嗯，我不知道。
Well, I don't know.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
嘿，你这个混蛋!
Hey, you son of a bitch!
我让她叫了，韦恩。
I had her barking, Wayne.
-你看到了吗?——是的。
- Did you see that? - Yep.
那是我的车。
That's my car there.
看到,850 - 263。——是啊，跟你的注册记录相符。
See that, 850-263. - Yeah,that checks with your registration.
你有钱把它弄出来吗?
You got the dough to get it out?
你在开玩笑吧?
Are you kidding?
不。
No.
是的，我有钱。
Yeah, I got the dough.
你需要多少，老爸?
How much you need, pops?
15美元,拖曳。
$15, towing.
5美元,存储。
$5, storage.
税是21美元。
And tax comes to $21.
嘿，这对你来说会容易很多。
Hey, this will make it a lot easier for you.
嘿，这是什么狗屁税收?
Hey, what's this tax crap here?
男人说:“收州税。”
The man says, "Collect the state tax."
所以我们征收州税。
So we collect the state tax.
法律不是我定的。
I don't make the laws.
是啊，我知道，你只是遵守它们，不是吗?
Yeah, I know, you just abide by them, don't you?
含税21美元，你有1美元吗?
It's $21 including tax, you got a dollar?
-是这样吗?-我感谢你们，国家感谢你们。
- Is that right? - I thank you and the state thanks you.
顺便说一下，你放在后座上的装备在后备箱里，这样就不会被偷了。
By the way, the gear you left in the back seat is in the trunk compartment so it wouldn't be stolen.
我感谢你，我的朋友也感谢你。
I thank you and my friend thanks you.
这老头。
That old fart.
税收，你能相信吗?
Tax, can you believe that?
他们会来抢你的车，收取你5美元的停车费，然后再向你收税。
They come snatch your car,charge you $5 storage and then they tax you to get it out.
该死的。
Goddamn.
税。
Tax.
嘿,女士。
Hey, ma'am.
男厕所在哪里?
Where's the men's restroom?
就在点唱机的左边。
It's right down there to the left of the jukebox.
好的，能再给我来点咖啡吗?
Okay, can I have some more coffee?
好的，再来一份吐司，好吗?
Yeah, and another order of toast, please?
你要加黄油吗?
You want it buttered?
是的。
Yeah.
嗨,弗兰克。
Hey, Frank.
嘿,弗娜。
Hey, Verna.
汤姆。-嗨。
Tom. - Hi.
来两杯咖啡，维娜。
Two cups of coffee, Verna.
给老汤姆一块苹果派。
And give old Tom here a piece of apple pie.
嘿，艾德，你怎么没去詹姆斯医生家?
Hey, Ed, how come you ain't over at Doc James' house?
斗鸡大约一点半开始。
Cockfight starts about 1:30.
你知道我再也不去看詹姆斯医生了。
You know I don't go to Doc James no more.
你更了解我，汤姆。
You know me better than that, Tom.
这是正确的。
That's right.
他靠经营经营赚的钱更多。
He makes more money running shine.
我再也不去看詹姆斯医生了。
I don't go to Doc James no more.
我检查,弗娜。
My check, Verna.
我不再去看詹姆斯医生了。
I don't go to Doc James anymore.
我不去看詹姆斯医生，已经有三四个星期没去了。
I don't go to Doc James,haven't been there for three or four weeks.
你就在那里。
There you are.
我再也不去看詹姆斯医生了。
I don't go to Doc James no more.
-嘿，艾德-我不去找詹姆斯医生
- Hey, Ed. - I don't go to Doc James.
嘿，艾德，继续回头看。
Hey, Ed, keep looking back.
是这样吗?
Is that right?
这是正确的。
That's right.
——谢谢。——嘿,弗娜,我们吃那个派吧。-你们都回来吧。
- Thank you. - Hey Verna,let's have that pie. - Y'all come back now.
好吧。
Okay.
那个孩子和另一个人?
That kid and that other guy?
他们刚把我从支票上扣了下来，去拿吧。
They just beat me from the check, go get them.
- - - - - -来吧。-抓住他们，弗兰克。
- Come on. - Get them, Frank.
该死的,快点。
Goddamn it, hurry.
我太想看到他们的脸了  我都想掉头回去了。
I wanna see their faces so bad I'm almost tempted to turn around and go back.
下次，狗娘养的，你喝咖啡我吃早餐，我饿死了。
Next time, son of a bitch, you drink the coffee and I eat the breakfast, I'm starved.
-你饿了吗?——我饿死了。
- Are you starved? - I'm starved.
给你些吐司，伙计。
Here's some toast, buddy.
哦，多谢了，冷吐司。
Oh, thanks a lot, cold toast.
嘘,嘘。
Psst, psst.
嘘。
Psst.
嘿。
Hey.
我要去达拉斯。
I'm going all the way to Dallas.
你一个人去。
You're going alone.
婊子。
Bitch.
记住,宝贝。
Now remember, baby.
写信到德克萨斯州达拉斯市453号邮政信箱，你会得到你的签名雕像
Write to P.O. Box 453 in Dallas, Texas and get your autographed statue...
嘿，看那个。
Hey, look at that.
耶稣基督在黑暗中发光
Of Jesus Christ that glows in the dark.
把它放在你的Studebaker上
Put it on your Studebaker.
现在有请卡尔·帕金斯先生
And now, Mr. Carl Perkins.
他有点白，但他还好
He's a little white, but he's all right.
嗨,红薯。
Hi, sweet potato.
-我叫珍妮·斯科特，好吗?——好的。
- Name's Jenny Scott, okay? - Okay.
我20岁了。
I'm 20 years old.
好。
Good.
昨天我被一个老南方男孩接走了。
Yesterday I got picked up by this old Southern boy.
他说我让他想起了他的女儿。
He said I reminded him of his daughter.
在她14岁的时候上了她。
Screwed her when she was 14.
今天有个古巴移民和他的胖老婆来接我。
Today this Cuban immigrant and his fat wife picked me up.
他不停地摸我的腿  而她却对此一笑置之。
He kept putting his goddamn hand on my leg and all she could do was laugh about it.
你们俩有什么打算?
So what do you two got in mind, hm?
我们只是想把手放在你腿上，仅此而已。
Oh, we just wanna put our hand on your leg, that's all.
于是法官说，“孩子，你会被判三年。你要么去参军，要么进监狱。
So the judge said,"Son, you're gonna get three years.You're either going in the military or you're going to jail.
我说，“法官大人，既然我不喜欢监禁，美军将在接下来的三年里拥有我。
I said, "Your Honor, since I'm not partial to incarceration, the United States Military's gonna have my company for the next three years.
然后他又入伍了这样我们就能加入伙伴制度了。
Then he re-enlisted so we could go in on the buddy system.
是啊，法官给了我们几周时间再入伍。
Yeah, the judge gave us a couple of weeks before we re-enlist.
所以这两周，我们就在外面鬼混，尽情狂欢。
So for these two weeks,we're just gonna be out catting around and having us a ball.
就这样，下周一，我们就走了。
That's it, a week from Monday, we're gone.
再见。
Goodbye.
但与此同时，你看。
But in the meantime, see.
嘿，别碰她的腿。
Hey, don't be touching her leg.
顺便说一下，这是我弟弟，韦恩，我是克里斯。
By the way this is my brother, Wayne, and I'm Chris.
-嗨。-嗨。
- Hi. - Hi.
你做了什么才被判三年的?
What did you do to get three years?
用专业术语来说，我所做的是什么?
Well, the technical term for what I did was,what was it?
这是用友方武器攻击，意图造成身体伤害。
It was assault with a friendly weapon with the intent of doing bodily harm.
都是他的错。
It's all his fault.
从我们小时候起，他就一直给我们惹麻烦。
Ever since we were kids,he's been getting us into trouble.
这是千真万确的事实。
That's the God's honest truth.
你就是那个总是给我们惹麻烦的人。
You're the one that's always getting us into trouble.
是我帮我们摆脱困境的。-你在说什么?
I'm the one that's getting us out of it. - What're you talking about?
你做了什么…-你开玩笑吧?
What did you do... - You shitting me?
我要，我是救我们出去的人。
I'm getting, I'm the one that gets us out.
那上次你在工地上用M-80向警长扔枪呢。
What about that time you threw an M-80 at that sheriff out there on that construction site.
-嘿，等一下。-就在他脑袋旁边爆炸了。——对不起。
- Hey, wait a minute. - It went off right next to his head. - Excuse me.
照亮了整个天空。
Lit up the whole sky.
-嘿，你可以跑的。-你做了什么被判三年?
- Hey, you could've run. - What did you do to get three years?
我做了。
I did run.
不，我跟你说，一切都始于，我打了我老妈
No, I tell you what, it all started,you see, when I hit my old lady.
你打了你妈妈，是吗?
You hit your mother, huh?
就几次，没什么大不了的。
Just a couple of times, it wasn't a big deal.
伟大的,为什么?
Great, great why?
我们在和她约会。
We were rolling some of her dates.
她觉得自己没有得到应得的那份面包。
And she didn't think that she was getting her fair share of the bread.
她以为我们把钱都装进了自己的口袋。
She thought we were pocketing all the money.
所以她像野兽一样冲过来   她的钉鞋正好打在了我的脖子后面。
So she charged at me like an animal and she sunk this spiked-heel shoe right in the back of my neck.
是吗?
Yeah?
事实上，你可以把手指插进去。
As a matter of fact,you can stick your finger in it.
就在这里，你的食指。
Right there, your index finger.
就在我的表皮丛里。
Right there in my cutepus plexus.
所以她，呃，当她这么做的时候，我就像那样喂了她一拳
And so she, uh,when she did that, I went like that and I fed her a knuckle sandwich.
是啊，我把她绑在了双导火索上  把她的脖子弯下来，把她撑起来。
Yeah, I had her in a double firebrand had her neck bent down, stretched her out.
我有它。
I had it.
韦恩，每次我们讲这个故事，都会越来越精彩。
Wayne, every time we tell that story,it gets better and better.
相信你所做的。
Sure you did.
——嗨,里德。——嗨,Gurn。
- Hi, Reed. - Hi, Gurn.
运来了一批艾萨卡斯。
Got a shipment of Ithacas in.
好价钱，在开季前打八折。
Good price, 20% off before the season starts.
这个你想卖多少钱?
Hey, uh,how much you want for this one?
哦，大概在60美元左右。
Oh, roughly in the neighborhood of $60.
加上你的折扣，大概是50美元。
Now, with your discount, that'll be about 50.
但你还想要把枪干什么?
But what do you want another gun for?
你一个月前就买了那辆勃朗宁。
You bought that Browning over and under a month back.
那不是给我的，是给卢克的。
That isn't for me, it's for Luke.
你为什么要给卢克买那样的大枪?
What do you wanna get Luke a big gun like that for?
我有一堆。410和20口径在后面  那对他来说很合适。
I got a bunch of. 410s and 20-gauges back there that'd be just right for him.
嘿，葛恩，过来。
Hey, Gurn, come here.
我去给卢克拿个12口径的。
I'm gonna get Luke a 12-gauge.
他能搞定我的。
He can handle mine pretty good.
他现在多大了?
How old is he now?
他是10。
He's 10.
管你呢。
The hell you say.
是的。
Yeah.
我十岁的时候就能很好地应付我爸的12口径手枪。
I could handle my daddy's 12-gauge pretty good when I was 10.
该死，我一定是老了。
Goddamn, I must be getting old.
我还记得你爸爸给你买的第一把枪。
I can remember when your daddy bought you your first gun.
但我发誓你比那个年纪大。
But I could've swore you were older than that.
当你到了我这个年纪时，头脑会捉弄你。
Mind plays tricks on you when you get my age.
除非你说的是钱。
Except when you're talking about money.
它来自于一种真正强烈的想要规律饮食的欲望。
It comes from a real strong desire to eat regular.
你看起来不像会错过很多晚餐。
Well, you don't look like you miss many meals.
你最多只能出50块?
Hey, 50 the best you can do?
是的。
Yep.
但我要20，你可以欠我30。
But I'll take 20 and you can owe me 30.
月底把钱付给我。
Pay me at the end of the month.
甚至不会收你任何利息。
Won't even charge you any interest.
好吧，那我给你十块钱怎么样?
Yeah, but, what about I give you 10?
瑞德，我的大脑不会对我耍那么多花招。
Reed, my mind don't play me that many tricks.
好吧。
Okay.
但听着，如果我晚一点还你剩下的钱，你可别生气。
But look it, don't get mad if I'm a little late in paying you the rest.
可能又是油泵的问题。
It's probably that fuel pump again.
你停车让我来开吧?
Why don't you pull over and let me drive?
你不累吗?
Aren't you tired?
不，我一点也不累。
No, I'm not tired at all.
好吧。
All right.
你想坐到后座上去好好爽一下吗?
You wanna get in the back seat and rack it up?
你知道我想要什么吗?
You know what I want?
我要一个花生酱和果冻三明治。
I want a peanut butter and jelly sandwich.
好吗?
Well?
你确定你不愿意用那匹母马  换四个翻新版和两个拖拉机轮胎吗?
Well, you're,you sure you won't trade that mare for the four retreads and the two tractor tires?
我跟你说过了，汉普，这匹母马是小马驹，你可以花一块钱买两匹。
I've told you, Hamp, the mare's in foal and you'd be getting two for the price of one.
没有,先生。
No, sir.
如果那匹母马没有产下小马驹，我就会给你四个改版。
If that mare hadn't been in foal,I would have given you the four retreads.
单是这匹马就值四个翻新版和四个拖拉机轮胎。
The mare alone is worth four retreads and four tractor tires.
你一定认为我是个乡巴佬才会同意这样的交易。
You must think I'm some kind of hick to go for a deal like that.
如果上帝要给这个世界灌肠  他就会在这里用软管。
If the Lord was gonna give the world an enema right here is where he'd stick the hose.
好。
Well.
去年，你说你想用母马换四个翻新版和两个拖拉机轮胎。
Last year, you said that you wanted to trade the mare for four retreads and two tractor tires.
我告诉过你我会考虑的，我已经考虑过了，你懂的。
And I told you I'd think about it,and I have thought about it you get the idea.
我要接受你的提议。
And I'm gonna take you up on your offer.
好吧，我告诉你。
Well, let me tell you something.
去年是七个月前。
Last year was seven months ago.
我已经从老吉姆·古奇那里拿到了翻新版和拖拉机轮胎。
And I already got the retreads and the tractor tires from old Jim Gooch.
我也不知道我们做交易的时候母马会产下马驹。
And I also didn't know the mare was gonna get herself in foal when we made the deal.
所以如果你还想要那匹母马，你就得加点甜头。
So if you still want that mare,you gotta sweeten the pie.
我现在得回家了以免丽塔开始嚷嚷我毁了她的晚餐。
Now, I gotta get home now before Rita starts yelling about my ruining her supper.
周日见。
I'll see you Sunday.
记住，如果你还在思考这个问题想想给派加糖。
And remember, if you're still thinking on it think of sweetening that pie.
再见。
Goodbye.
待会儿见。
I'll see you later on.
汉普，你找到那匹母马了吗?
Hamp, did you get the mare?
不，不，他说他会考虑一下然后周日告诉我们。
No, no, he said he's gonna think on it and let us know Sunday.
我几个月前就叫你去换那匹母马了  但你一直说他只能换四个翻新的
I told you to trade for that mare months ago but you kept saying he'd come down to four retreads.
好吧,他没有。
Well, he didn't.
现在他正在思考这个问题。
And now he's thinking on it.
你们俩之间，什么都不能做。
Between the two of you, nothing never be done.
她是我生活的祸害。
Oh, she's the bane of my existence.
我可以填满吗?
Can I fill it?
没有,先生。
No, sir.
是燃油泵的问题。
It's the fuel pump.
不是卡住了就是坏了。
Think it's either jammed or broken.
让我看看。
Let me see it.
像这样多久了?
How long has it been like that?
挺长时间了，但我们还是走到了这一步。
Oh, quite some time,but it got us to here, though.
好吧，你不会有别的地方了。
Well, it won't get you any place else.
你看到那个球了吗?
You see that catch there?
是的。
Yeah.
你得把那个钓索修好，不然它会掉下去。
You gotta fix that catch before it'll go any place.
现在，你需要的是一个新泵。
Now, what you need is a new pump.
我们卖新的泵。
And we sell new pumps.
嗨,蜂蜜。
Hi, honey.
嗨。
Hi.
嘿，你怎么回来了?
Hey, what are you doing home?
我得换件衬衫。
I gotta change this shirt.
外面太热了。
It's so damn hot out there.
嘿,李在哪儿?
Hey, where's Lee?
他打电话说他不来了。
Oh, he called to say he wasn't coming by.
他不得不去看医生治疗糖尿病。
And he had to go to the doctor about his diabetes.
糖尿病
Diabetes.
他只是宿醉没醒，就这样。
He's just hung-over, that's all.
我觉得我们永远都建不了新房子了。
I don't think we're ever gonna get that new house built.
在李看来，一切都结束了。
As far as Lee's concerned, it's finished.
他还没开始呢。
He hasn't even started on it yet.
嘿。
Hey.
抢手货。
Good catch.
嘿,你饿了吗?
Hey, you hungry?
没有，我之前吃过东西了。
No, man, I had something to eat earlier.
那是一把新枪吗?
Is that a new gun?
哦,是的。
Oh, yeah.
在轮尼医院有个交易。
Got a deal on it down at Gurney's.
他说我月底前都不用给他钱。
Said I didn't have to pay him till the end of the month.
我的信用很好。
My credit's good.
这是给卢克的惊喜。
It's a surprise for Luke.
能给我拿瓶啤酒吗?
Would you get me a beer?
卡萝，你能帮我拿一个吗?
Carol, would you get me a?
能给我拿瓶啤酒吗?
Oh, would you get me a beer?
嘿，先生，我想我们最好去拿那个油泵。
Hey, mister, I guess we'd better go and take that fuel pump.
那你能付得起钱吗?
Well, can you pay for it?
是的，我有信用卡。
I got a credit card, yeah.
我不打卡。
Well, I don't take cards.
为什么不呢，见鬼，这很好。
Why not, hell, it's good.
你可以去看看。
You can check it out.
他们负责拿到钱。
They're responsible for getting the money.
我们在路易斯安那州和阿拉巴马州使用过。
We used it in Louisiana, Alabama.
佛罗里达、密西西比。
Florida, Mississippi.
不，我不打卡。
No, I don't take cards.
我们甚至用它买了个轮胎。
We even bought a tire with it.
我跟你说，我拿过一次卡，以后就不收了
I'll tell you, I took cards once,I don't take them no more.
明白了吗?
You get the idea?
要么付现金，要么刷卡。
It's either cash or charge.
好吧，我们来刷卡。
All right, we'll charge it.
你不能刷卡。
You can't charge it.
我不知道你是谁。
I don't know who you are.
你得付现金。
You're just gonna have to pay cash.
多少钱?
How much is it?
好的，请稍等，我查查看。
Well, just a second, I'll check.
我们有多少钱?
How much we got?
我有3块，你有多少?
I got $3, how much you got?
我有四个。
I got four.
含税一共27美元。
That's, uh, $27 including tax.
克里斯。
Chris.
什么?
What?
我收到3美元。
I got $3.
不，没关系。
No, that's all right.
把枪。
Get the gun.
什么枪?
What gun?
把枪。
Get the gun.
你看到了吗?
You see that?
泵动。
Pump-action.
那是一把22口径的步枪。
That's a.22 caliber rifle.
现在，我们要做的是用这个换你的燃油泵。
Now, what we wanna do is trade you that for that fuel pump.
哦。
Oh.
我告诉你，我用不了a。22。
Well, I'll tell you, I got no use for a.22.
嘿，你有猎枪吗?
Hey, you got a shotgun?
我需要一把猎枪。
I could use a shotgun.
我来告诉你我们要做什么。
I'll tell you what we'll do.
我们跟你交换这个。22步枪和8。3美元的燃油泵。
We'll trade you this.22 rifle and that $8.30 for a fuel pump.
现在，这是一个便宜货。
Now, that's a bargain.
不，不，我用不了a。22。
No, no, I got no use for a.22.
他不是说他可以用钩子什么的暂时修好它吗?
Didn't he say he could fix it temporarily with a catch or something?
你不是这么说的吗?
Didn't you say that?
你说了，不是吗?
You did, didn't you?
那要花多少钱?
How much would that cost?
是啊，我花五块钱就能修好，但也不会让你跑多远。
Yeah, I could fix that for about five bucks,but it wouldn't take you very far.
大概20英里左右吧，我不知道。
Maybe 20 miles or so, I don't know.
看，离这里最近的车站有多远?
Look, how far is the nearest station from here?
这取决于你往哪个方向走。
Well, that would depend on which direction you're going in.
嗯，我们要往西走，但我们得先到最近的车站。
Well, we're going west, but we have to go to the nearest station first.
哦，韦斯特，让我想想。
Oh, west, well, let's see.
也许，梅肯在这里，85英里，但是。
That's probably,well, Macon's down here, 85 miles, but.
好吧，让我考虑一下。
Well, let me think on it a minute.
花你的时间。
Take your time.
让我看看，你走到这，然后你会摇摆
Let's see, you go down here and you'd swing around
哦，是的，是的，是的。
oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
那里有个加油站。
They got a gas station there.
,在这里吗?
Where, down here?
不，在桑顿这里。
No, over here in Thornton.
它是。
It's.
是多少，40?
What is it, 40?
我觉得有40英里。
I'd say it's 40 miles.
有45英里，你明白吗?
It's 45 miles, you get the idea?
是啊，我以前也在那放过油。
Yeah, I got gas there myself once.
他们会收你的信用卡。
They'll take your credit card for you.
听着，去做那笔交易吧，你花5美元修理一下，你知道的，暂时的。
Look, go ahead and do that deal where you fix it for $5, you know temporarily.
如果你能在天黑前搞定，我们会很感激的。
We'd appreciate it if you could do that before it gets dark.
我们得离开这里，去警局。
We gotta get out of here so we can go to the station.
——当然,是的。——好吧?
- Sure, yeah. - All right?
就算我抓对了人，也得花点时间。
Well, even if I do have the right catch,it's gonna take a little while.
你的洗手间在哪里?
Say, where's your restroom?
就在这里就在后面。
It's right oh, it's right around in the back here.
到处走走，那里有个标志。
Just swing around, there's a sign there.
就在招牌附近。
It's right near the sign.
在那里?
Right around there?
是啊，我得去看看我有没有抓到把柄。
Yeah, I gotta go see if I got the catch.
好吧。
Okay.
天啊，我真希望他能补上这一招。
Man, I sure hope he can fix that catch.
我可不想在这地方耽搁时间。
I'd hate to get hung up in this place.
天啊，你说得对。
Boy, you can say that again.
天啊，我真希望他能补上这一招。
Man, I sure hope he can fix that catch.
我可不想在这地方耽搁时间。
I'd hate to get hung up in this place.
嘘。
Boo.
你觉得那个女孩怎么样?
What do you think of that girl?
哦，她很好。
Oh, she's all right.
是的，她很好。
Yeah, she is all right.
你看到她多快就弄到钱了吗?
Did you see how fast she came up with that money?
她本可以一走了之的。
She could've just left, you know.
你觉得我们能和那个妞搞到一起吗?
Well, you think we're gonna score with that broad?
这算什么"我们"啊?
What's this we shit, huh?
她说你有口臭。
She said you had bad breath.
她没那么说。
She didn't say that.
是的,她做的。
Yeah, she did.
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious, huh?
离开这里。
Get out of here.
-嗨。-嗨。
- Hi. - Hi.
你有多余的牙刷吗?
Have you got an extra toothbrush?
不，我有我自己的。
No, I just got my own.
你想用吗?
You wanna use it?
嗯?
Huh?
你想用吗?
Do you wanna use it?
是的，如果可以的话。
Yeah, if it's all right.
确定。
Sure.
如果上面没有任何食物的话。
If it doesn't have any food on it.
——哦,克里斯?——什么?
- Oh, Chris? - What?
用这个可能会容易些。
Might be a little easier with this.
——再见。——谢谢。
- Bye. - Thank you.
嘿，艾达，怎么了?
Hey, Ida, what's going on?
里德，你这个帅呆了的混蛋。
Reed, you good-looking son of a gun.
你不应该把尸体吓个半死。
You're not supposed to scare a body half to death.
你们进来的时候弄出点声音来。
Now, make some damn noise when y'all come in.
声音?
Noise?
该死，我弄出的声音都能把死人吵醒了。
Hell, I made enough noise to wake the dead.
珍妮?
Jenny?
来了。
Coming.
肯定是果冻，因为果酱不会那样摇晃。
Must be jelly, because jam don't shake like that.
天啊，好热。
Oh, God, it's hot.
嘿。
Hey.
艾达，我不相信你。
Hey, Ida, I don't believe you.
你作弊。
You're cheating.
现在我知道你为什么不愿称体重了。
Now I know why you won't get on that scale.
我一看临床医学书籍就紧张。
Oh, I get nervous when I read them clinical books.
临床吗?
Clinical?
临床、我的屁股。
Clinical, my ass.
你只是喜欢给他们看黄书，仅此而已。
You just like reading them dirty books, that's all.
你知道那不是事实。
You know that ain't the truth.
我只是在生意不好的时候坐在这里  对着那个懒汉大喊大叫会很紧张。
I just get nervous sitting around here when business is slow and yelling at that lazy Hamp.
加满油，爸爸。
Fill it up, dad.
艾达，别跟我说那个但是，但是。
Hey, Ida, don't give me that but, but.
你听起来像Hamp。
You sound like Hamp.
你知道吗，事实是你根本没有你一直吹嘘的勇气。
Hey, you know, the truth of the matter is that you just ain't got all that intestinal fortitude you was always bragging about.
看那边。
Look over there.
他们比我早来多久了?
How long they been here before me?
他们三个孩子?
Them three kids?
是的。
Yep.
我猜他们是在奥吉离开的时候来的。
I guess they got here about the time that Augie left.
那一定是15分钟前的事了。
Oh, that must have been about 15 minutes ago.
快点起来。
Hurry it up.
爸，我说了快点。
Hey, dad, I said hurry it up.
足够了。
Enough.
放轻松，朗。
Take it easy, Lon.
快点，快点。
Come on, hurry it up.
我知道你需要的是啤酒。
I know what you need is a beer.
我不需要警察。
Well, I don't need no cops.
Hamp贷款吗?
Hamp?
嘿,Hamp贷款?
Hey, Hamp?
Hamp贷款!
Hamp!
Hamp，你在后面吗?
Hamp, are you back there?
是的，我在后面，在后面。
Yeah, I'm back here in the back.
你的车真不错。
Sure is a nice car you got there.
我就知道是你，里德。
I thought that was you, Reed.
我以为你在为明天的大日子做准备呢。
I figured you'd be getting ready for the big day tomorrow.
你知道，狩猎季节开始了。
Hunting season starts, you know.
我是。
I am.
我现在要去胡德的军校接卢克。
I'm on my way to pick up Luke over at military school in Hood right now.
你知道他刚当上警督吗?
Hey, you know he just made lieutenant?
在军队里，挣得最多的就是上士。
In the Army, I never made more than staff sergeant.
你到底在找什么?
What the hell are you looking for?
哦，我在找机会。
Oh, I'm looking for a catch.
抓，抓什么?
Catch, catch for what?
外面那辆别克车里的水泵。
A catch for that,for the water pump in that Buick outside.
Hamp，那不是别克，那是克莱斯勒。
Hamp, that's not a Buick, that's a Chrysler.
那我找错地方了。
I'm looking in the wrong place then.
孩子们需要的是一个新水泵。
What them kids need anyway is a new pump.
但他们没钱付钱。
But they ain't got the money to pay for it.
好吧，再见。
Yeah, well, see you.
是的。
Yeah.
有什么麻烦吗?
What's the trouble?
我们的燃油泵卡住了。
Our fuel pump's jammed up.
连杆在上面失灵了。
The linkage is messed up on it.
你们从哪来?
Where y'all from?
芝加哥。
Chicago.
你在这里做什么?
Well, uh, what are you doing here?
我们只是路过，直到我们的车抛锚了。
We were just passing through,until our car broke down.
一旦修好，我们就会继续前进。
Soon as we get it fixed, we'll be moving on.
如果你能影响到广场上的人，我们会很感激的。
If you got any influence on hurrying the square in there, we'd appreciate it.
是的，Hamp有时候有点慢。
Yeah, Hamp is kind of slow sometimes.
你们现在不介意给我看看你的证件吧?
Say, y'all wouldn't mind showing me some identification now, would you?
不。
No.
不，一点也不。
No, not at all.
我想我钓到一条会管用的鱼了。
I think I got me a catch that's gonna work.
你在哪里?
Where you been?
把它拿出来，好吗?
Take it out, will you?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
在新奥尔良。
Down in New Orleans.
是吗?
Yeah?
你在那儿干什么?
What were you doing there?
我去体检了。
I went down there to take my physical.
你从达拉斯吗?
You from Dallas?
是的,是的。
Yeah, yeah.
把你的身体吗?
Take your physical?
身体为了什么?
Physical for what?
的军队。
For the Army.
你被征召了吗?
Did you get drafted?
不,我参军。
No, I enlisted.
继续。
Go on.
你在开玩笑吧?
You're kidding?
不。
No.
你参军?
You enlisted?
是的。
Yeah.
给你。
Here you go.
告诉我，你身上带钱了吗?
Say, uh, tell me, you got some money on you?
是的,为什么?
Yeah, why?
你得给我10块，总共30块   否则你就是流浪汉。
Well, you see, you've got to have $10 a piece, 30 total or you're considered vagrants.
你知道那是什么，对吧?
You know what that is, don't you?
是的,流浪者。
Yeah, vagrants.
是的，我知道那是什么。
Yeah, I know what that is.
瞧，我们这里有条法律。
See, we got a law here.
你一定要有那30美元。
You got to have that $30.
你想给我看看吗?
You wanna show it to me?
不，我不想去。
No, I'd rather not.
我想我明白你的意思。
I think I know what you mean.
你是说你会在汉普修完车后马上离开吗?
You say you're gonna be moving on just as quick as Hamp finishes working on the car?
越快越好，好的，先生。
Just as soon as possible, yes, sir.
没别的理由再待下去了，是吧?
Got no reason to stick around for nothing else, do you?
不。
No.
好。
Good.
不，等修好了，我们就走，修好了就走。
No, as soon as we get it fixed,we're moving out, just as soon as we get it fixed.
这是真正的好。
That's real good.
嘿,Hamp
Hey, Hamp.
是吗?
Yeah?
那边，快上车。
Hurry up on the car, there.
除非万不得已，我们不想让这些人在这里待太久。
Don't wanna keep these nice folk here any longer than we have to.
他们可能会慢慢喜欢上的。
They might grow to like it.
我一点也不喜欢那样。
I wouldn't like that at all.
好,看到你。
Well, see you.
那是什么?
What was that?
愚蠢的乡巴佬。
Dumb hick.
特里?
Terry?
芦苇。
Reed.
给我一辆48年伊利诺斯州车牌Town & Country克莱斯勒敞篷车，850-263。
Give me a make on a 48 Town & Country Chrysler convertible illinois plates, 850-263.
这是850 - 263。
That's 850-263.
好吧?
Okay?
然后尽快给我答复，好吗?
And get back to me quick as you can, will ya?
好的
Will do.
嘿,比尔?
Hey, Bill?
嗯嗯?
Mm-hm?
里德需要马上做个调查。
Reed needs a make on this right away.
他是好的吗?
Is he okay?
是的，他很好。
Yeah, he's all right.
只是我们已经在一起很久很久了。
It's just that we've been together for a long, long time.
嘿，那边那个地方怎么样?
Hey, how about that place there?
它和其他的一样好。
It's as good as any.
让我们得到它。
Let's get it.
先生。
Sir.
摩根先生，我来接我儿子卢克。
Mr. Morgan, I'm here to pick up my son, Luke.
类,10-hut。
Class, 10-hut.
中尉摩根,解雇。
Lieutenant Morgan, dismissed.
类,请坐。
Class, be seated.
——嗨,儿子。——嗨,爸爸。
- Hi, son. - Hi, dad.
嘿，让我看看你。
Hey, let me look at you.
那些警督酒吧看起来真不错。
Those lieutenant bars really look good.
你让你妈妈和我都为你骄傲。
You made your mom and me mighty proud.
嘿，明天和我一起去打猎怎么样?
Hey, how about going hunting with me tomorrow?
我一定要去吗，爸爸?
Do I have to go, dad?
我还想做些别的事。
There were some other things I wanted to do.
不，你不必去，孩子 我很想和你待一会儿。
No, you don't have to go, boy but I sure would like to spend some time with you.
你知道吗，自从你来这里上学我们就没怎么在一起过，都没时间说话。
You know, since you've been going to school here we haven't been together too much,haven't had any time to talk.
我也想去，但我想和海盗们一起打球。
I'd like to go, but I wanna play ball with the Pirates.
他们是杰夫·戴维斯家的几个孩子。
They're some of the kids from Jeff Davis.
他们要我加入他们的队伍，我答应了。
They asked me to be on their team and I said I would.
好吧，如果你答应过。
Well, if you promised.
是的，爸爸，真的。
I did, dad, honest.
卢克，你觉得他们会介意你不去吗?
Hey, Luke, do you think they'd mind very much if you didn't?
不，孩子，你去跟他们玩吧。
No, son, you go ahead and play with them.
我们下周末去打猎。
We'll go hunting next weekend.
谢谢，爸爸，他们真的很需要我。
Thanks, dad, they really need me.
我是个好击球手。
I'm a good hitter.
嘿，你和妈妈为什么不来看比赛呢?
Hey, why don't you and Mom come to the game?
我想妈妈不会去的。
I don't think Mom would go.
你知道她有多担心你。
You know how she worries about you.
她甚至不想让我明天带你去打猎。
She didn't even want me to take you hunting tomorrow.
或者任何一天都可以。
Or any day, for that matter.
哦,男孩。
Oh, boy.
Luke?
来吧，我们回家吧。
Come on, let's go home.
下周见，詹姆斯。
See you next week, James.
再见,Luke。
See you, Luke.
再见,查尔斯。
Bye, Charles.
你没有体面的感觉吗?
Have you left no sense of decency?
我知道这伤害了你，韦尔奇先生
I know this hurts you, Mr. Welch.
参议员，我想这也伤害了你，先生
Senator, I think it hurts you too, sir.
我想把这个做完。
I'd like to finish this.
他每天都在说  他想在日落前把任何被共产主义玷污的人赶出去。
He's been talking day after day about the way he wants to get anyone tainted with communism out before sundown.
军队与麦卡锡的争议  今天爆发了新的耸人听闻的指控和否认，涉及到艾森豪威尔政府的另一位高级官员。
The Army-McCarthy controversy erupted today with new sensational charges and denials involving another high official of the Eisenhower administration.
这么多天来，一直在党团会议大厅为约瑟夫·麦卡锡参议员鼓掌的人群突然沉默下来。
The crowds that had long applauded senator Joseph McCarthy in the Caucus Room for so many days were suddenly silent.
他们似乎有了一个新的英雄，也叫乔.约瑟夫·韦尔奇。
They seem to have acquired a new hero,also named Joe. Joseph Welch.
韦尔奇先生
Mr. Welch.
不，不，不，别吵。
No, no, no, don't make a noise.
Had been针刺他…
Had been needling him...
嗨,妈妈。
Hi, Momma.
如果你不发出声音，我们就不会伤害你。
We ain't gonna hurt you if you don't make no noise.
我们只是来拿点东西。
We just came to take a few things.
证人在麦卡锡面前的声音
Witnesses had sounded in front of McCarthy.
韦尔奇进门时，麦卡锡开始局促不安
As Welch bore in, McCarthy began squirming.
你看到了什么?
You see?
他的助手接受了他所享受的惩罚
His aide took the punishment he enjoyed.
那是我的朋友。
That's my friend over here.
韦尔奇成为了一名特别军事顾问，这是众所周知的事。
It was common knowledge that Mr. Welch became a special Army counsel.
他曾考虑聘请年轻的律师弗雷德·费希尔。
He had considered using the young attorney named Fred Fisher.
然而,学习。
Learning, however.
朗，你说得对，周围没人。
Lon, you're right, there ain't nobody around.
韦尔奇,让更多。
Welch, toward making additional.
我要把你带回去，绑在房间里，这样你就不会弄出太多噪音。
I'm gonna take you back and tie you up in the room,just so you don't make a lot of noise.
你别动，我们不会伤害你的。
You stay still and we won't hurt you at all.
来吧,妈妈。
Come on, Momma.
来吧。
Come on.
-求你了-没事的妈妈
- Please - No, it's all right, Momma.
只是坐下来。
Just sit down.
我要把你绑起来。
I'm gonna tie you up.
那是你爸爸吗，妈妈?
That your old man, Momma?
你老爸是警察?
Your old man a cop?
他是个大男人，对吧，妈妈?
He's a big man, huh, Momma?
他一周给你几次，妈妈?
How many times a week does he give it to you, Momma?
他是自己拿的还是自己要的，妈妈?
Does he take it from you or does he ask you for it, Momma?
请
Please
嘿，需要男人吗，妈妈?
Hey, need a man, Momma?
不!
No!
它在我们身上。
It's pegging on us.
他说至少能开20英里。
He said it'd get at least 20 miles.
嗯,差不多。
Well, almost.
我们只差10英里了。
Hell, we're only 10 miles short.
他已经尽力了。
Well, hell, he did the best he could.
他花了大约五个小时。
He worked on it for about five hours.
唯一的问题是他的智商只有八。
The only problem was he had an IQ of about eight.
你好,阳光。
Hello, sunshine.
你睡了吗?
Did you sleep?
是的，有一点。
Yeah, a little bit.
这辆车怎么了?
What's the matter with the car?
这是胡来了。
It's crapping out.
就这样了，伙计，我们买下来了。
Well, that's it, man, we bought it.
不会再继续下去了。
It's not going any further.
我来告诉你我是干什么的。
I'll tell you what I'm for.
睡一觉，明天再考虑吧。
Get some sleep and worry about it tomorrow.
现在我们也无能为力了。
There's nothing we can do about it now anyways.
我想你是对的。
I think you're right.
明天早上我们搭便车去桑顿拿个燃油泵自己把它接上。
Tomorrow morning we'll hitch a ride to Thornton get a fuel pump and hook it up ourselves.
你能做到，不是吗?
You can do that, can't you?
我不知道，如果我有合适的工具，我可能会，我不知道。
I don't know, if I had the right tools,I might be able to, I don't know.
什么意思，如果你有工具?
What do you mean, if you had the tools?
什么，你要被哄着吗?
What, you gotta be coaxed?
这和被哄骗无关。
It has nothing to do with being coaxed.
我只是不知道我能不能做到。
I just don't know if I can do it.
如果你不。
If you don't.
如果你不解决，我们就会陷入困境。
If you don't fix it, we're stuck.
现在，我只想睡个好觉。
Right now, all I care about is getting some sleep.
我们可以明天再担心。
We can worry about it tomorrow.
也许车会被拖走——我们根本就不用担心了。
Maybe the car will get towed off we won't have to worry about it at all.
我们要让珍妮伸出她的腿，好让我们搭便车。
We'll get Jenny out there to stick out her leg so we can hitchhike.
那样我们就没人骑了。
We wouldn't get any rides that way.
我想说的是，如果我们不修好它，我们就会被困住。
All that I'm saying is,if we don't get it fixed, we're stuck.
这就是我要说的。
That's all I'm saying.
好了,我们被困住了。
Okay, we're stuck.
我他妈该怎么做?
What the hell am I supposed to do about it?
那我们睡会儿吧，好吗?
Let's get some sleep then, okay?
这辆车归我。
Dibs on the car.
不，我们得找个地方睡觉。
No, we gotta look for a place to sleep.
好。
Good.
我们应该做的是在车上留个便条以防警长来过这里。
You know, what we ought to do is put a note on the car in case that sheriff came by here.
你不觉得吗?
Don't you think?
韦恩?
Well, Wayne?
好吧，我会的。
All right, I'll do it.
什么?
What?
我说过我会做的。
I said I'd do it.
我告诉你吧。
I'll tell you what.
你们俩解决我们的问题。
You two solve our problem.
我要去车里睡觉了。
I'm gonna go sleep in the car.
晚安,韦恩。
Good night, Wayne.
(他为什么这么不高兴?)
What's he so upset about?
我不知道。
I don't know.
可能是因为只有一个女孩。
It's probably because there's just one girl.
到这里来。
Come here.
你还没告诉我们你为什么要去达拉斯。
You never did tell us why you were going to Dallas.
我在这家酒吧工作，他们发现我未成年。
Well, I was working in this bar and they found out I was underage.
他们怎么知道的?
How'd they find that out?
我有一个室友，我们经常在一起聊天，有天晚上我们交换了生活中的故事。
I had a roommate and we talked a lot together and one night we exchanged life stories.
酒吧的经理是她的男朋友。
See, the manager of the bar was her boyfriend.
哦。
Oh.
,嗯。
And, uh.
他看我的次数开始多于看她的次数。
He kind of started looking at me more than he did her.
总之，有一晚他跟我调情。
Anyway, one night,one night he made a pass at me.
,嗯。
And, uh.
不知怎么的，她发现了。
Somehow she found out about it.
我不知道，也许他已经告诉她了。
I don't know, maybe he even told her.
有趣的是你从没告诉过我  你为什么要去达拉斯。
You know, what's funny is you never did tell me why you were going to Dallas.
这有关系吗?
Look, does it matter?
不，没关系。
No, it doesn't matter.
那为什么还要问?
Well, then why ask?
我很感兴趣，好奇或者。
I was interested or curious or.
见鬼，我也不知道。
Hell, I don't know.
儿子吗?
Son?
是的,先生?
Yes, sir?
你还记得我们离开学校时你向他招手的那个男孩吗?
You know that boy you waved to back there as we left school?
是的，先生，他叫詹姆斯。
Yes, sir, his name's James.
你怎么认识他的，孩子?
How do you know him, son?
他不上你们学校，是吗?
He doesn't go to your school, does he?
嗯，有一天自习结束后，我有一些空闲时间，所以我去了篮球场，他们在那里。
Well, one day after study hall,I had some free time so I went to use the basketball court and there they were.
我们选了队，到目前为止，我们队在10场比赛中赢了7场。
We chose up teams, and so far my team's won seven out of 10 games.
但我觉得学校不希望他们去。
But I don't think the school wants them there.
他们已经跑了好几次了。
They've been run off a couple of times.
你知道在学校你必须遵守规章制度吗?
You know how in school you have rules and laws that you have to follow?
就像你要遵守法律一样。
Just like you have laws to follow.
正确的。
Right.
好。
Well.
在萨特，他们只是。
At Sutter, they just.
他们只是不接受黑人，仅此而已。
They just don't take blacks, that's all.
不是因为他们没钱，而是他们不收钱。
Not because they don't have the money,but they just don't take them.
但是，爸爸，这好像不对。
But, dad, that doesn't seem right.
学校认为黑人应该和其他黑人一起上学   白人应该和其他白人一起上学，孩子。
The school feels that blacks should go to school with other blacks and whites should go with other whites, son.
这样事情就简单多了。
It just seems to make things a whole lot easier.
你妈妈和我也是这么想的。
Your mom and I feel the same way.
那是不是意味着我不能再和他们一起打篮球了?
Does that mean I can't play basketball with them anymore?
我希望你不要。
I wish you wouldn't.
好吧?——好的。
Okay? - Okay.
谢谢。
Thanks.
非常感谢。
Thanks a lot.
你看看，好吗?
Look at that, will you?
我想我最好让他们靠边停车  告诉他们把灯修好  免得他们屁股被撞坏了。
I think I'd better have them pull over and tell them to get their lights fixed before their ass-end gets bashed in.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
我们穿这玩意跑不过他们。
We can't outrun them in this thing.
我要靠边停车。
I'm gonna pull over.
不要这样做。
Don't do it.
不要崩溃。
Don't you fall apart.
闭上你的嘴。
Just keep your mouth shut.
-你好。-嗨。
- Howdy. - Hi.
我看见你开车经过。
I seen you drive by.
我注意到你的尾灯坏了。
I noticed your taillights were out.
不想让别人撞见你。
Didn't want nobody to run into you.
该死，他们一定是出去了。
Damn they must have just gone out.
我们在路上加油的时候他们正在工作。
They were working when we got gas back down the road.
好的，我会把它们修好的。
Well, I'll get them fixed.
是啊，我要是你就这么做。
Yeah, I'd do that if I were you.
不想让你们都受伤。
Don't want y'all to get hurt.
你会发现六英里外有个车站。
Now, you'll find a station about six miles.
一直沿着高速公路走。
Just keep following the highway.
嘿,比尔,
Hey, Bill,
看看后座上的这些东西。
look at this stuff here in the back seat.
好了，你们都下车。
All right, you guys, get out of the car.
——我们死了。——继续开车。
- We're dead. - Keep driving.
36号车，代码10
Car 36, code 10.
重复、代码10。
Repeat, code 10.
我正在追踪一辆新款史蒂贝克车  在特纳路209号路口向北行驶。
I'm in pursuit of a late-model Studebaker heading north on Turner Road near Junction 209.
所有单位请回复10号代码。
All available units respond to code 10.
我知道他们会抓到我们的。
I know they're gonna get us.
来吧，开车。
Come on and drive.
我们死了。
We're dead.
朗。
Lon.
你来吧。
You come on.
你开车像个女人。
You're driving like a woman.
我们会成功的。
We're gonna make it.
不，我们不会的。
No, we ain't gonna.
我们不会，我知道，我看得出来。
We're not gonna, I know, I can see.
别再让他们抓到我了。
Don't let them get me again.
你别再哭哭啼啼地开车了。
You quit sniveling and drive.
天啊，如果他抓到我，我就杀了你。
Oh, boy, if he catches me, I'm gonna kill you.
当心那辆卡车!
Look out for that truck!
Luke?
嗨,Luke。
Hey, Luke.
你没事吧，孩子，醒醒。
You all right, boy, wake up.
卢克。
Luke.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
是的，我只是做了个梦，爸爸。
Yeah, I was only having a dream, dad.
好吧，你让我担心了。
Oh, okay, you had me worried.
-比尔，我想和你谈谈-威廉姆斯先生
- Bill, I wanna talk - Mr. Williams.
我的搭档有妻子和两个孩子  我刚跟他们谈过。
My partner had a wife and two kids and I just got done talking to them.
但我是法庭指派来维护这些人的权利的  他们有权见自己的律师。
But I'm appointed by the court to defend these people's rights and they have a right to see their attorney.
我什么时候可以看?
When can I see them?
-等我准备好了。——比尔。
- When I'm good and ready. - Bill.
把你的脚从桌子上拿开。
Get your foot off the table.
好了，把手铐解开。
All right, take the cuffs off this garbage.
恰克，出去喝杯咖啡。
Chuck, go out and get yourself some coffee.
好吧，签了这些文件。
Okay, sign these papers.
对什么?
What for?
这些是被你这人渣杀的警察的招供。
These are confessions for the cop you scum killed.
我不会认罪的。
I ain't signing no confession.
爸，我想和公设辩护律师谈谈。
Hey, dad, I wanna talk to the public defender.
你签了供词就能见到他了。
You'll see him after you sign these confessions.
现在签字。
Now sign them.
我不会认罪的。
I ain't signing no confession.
我们知道我们的权利。
We know what our rights are.
废话。
Bullshit.
在我看来，你没有任何权利。
You ain't got no rights as far as I'm concerned.
现在开始吧。
Now get to it.
我什么都不会签的。
I ain't signing nothing.
把你的手放在桌子上。
Put your hands on the table.
对什么?
What for?
我说，把手放在桌子上。
I said, put your hands on the table.
平，你个混蛋，平。
Flat, you son of a bitch, flat.
现在你是右撇子还是左撇子?
Now you right-handed or left-handed?
我是右撇子。
I'm right-handed.
现在，要么你开始写作，要么你马上就会变成左撇子。
Now, either you start writing or you're gonna become left-handed immediately.
等一下。
Wait a minute.
嘿,男人。
Hey, man.
嘿,先生。
Hey, sir.
嘿,男人。
Hey, man.
嘿，别忘了你的手提箱。
Hey, don't forget your suitcase.
哦,是的。
Oh, yeah.
,快点进去。
And hurry inside.
我有个惊喜给你。
I got a surprise for you.
嗨,Luke。
Hey, Luke.
现在仔细听我说，孩子。
Now listen to me carefully, boy.
你待在这里，别动。
You stay right here, now, don't move.
怎么了，爸爸?
What's the matter, dad?
你留在这儿，现在。
You stay here, now.
妈妈?
Mom?
妈妈!
Mother!
Momma!
——那是什么?-起床，穿好衣服。
- What's that? - Get up, get dressed.
Luke!
来吧。——母亲。
Come on. - Mother.
妈妈,妈妈。——Luke、Luke。
Mother, mother. - Luke, Luke.
该死的，闭嘴!——母亲。
Goddamn it, shut up! - Mother.
闭嘴，闭嘴!
Shut up, shut up!
现在,来吧!
Now, come on!
伙计，快点，我们离开这鬼地方。
Man, come on, let's get the hell out of here.
他疯了，他朝我开枪。
He's crazy, he shot at me.
警长带着枪来了。
Sheriff's coming with a gun.
走吧，快离开这鬼地方。
Let's go, get the hell out of here.
特里?
Terry?
芦苇。
Reed.
马上派辆救护车来我家。
Send an ambulance to my place right away.
这些垃圾是什么?
What's all this junk?
这是从嫌疑犯的车里拿到的证据。
This is the evidence taken from the suspects' car.
安妮，检查一下电视机的序列号。
Annie, run a serial-number check on the TV set.
尽你所能去看看其余的东西。
Check out the rest of the stuff as best you can.
——比尔?-是的。
- Bill? - Yeah.
里德让我派辆救护车去他家  然后他关掉了收音机。
Reed told me to send an ambulance to his house and then he turned off the radio.
我无法让他回来。
I can't get him back.
我给他家打了电话，但没人接。
I dialed his home but there's no answer there.
我很担心你。-这一切是什么时候发生的?
I'm worried. - When did all this happen?
大约五分钟前。
About five minutes ago.
他还说了什么吗?
Did he say anything else?
不，但外面出事了，得有人去。
No, but something is wrong out there and somebody ought to go.
他什么都没说，是吧?
He said nothing, huh?
听着，你一直在用无线电跟他说话。
Look, you keep trying to raise him on the radio.
安妮，快接电话。
Annie, get busy on the phone.
我在外面给你打电话。
I'll call you from out there.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
那狗娘养的疯了，伙计。
That son of a bitch is crazy, man.
来吧,男孩。
Come on, boy.
来吧,Luke。
Come on, Luke.
持有它。
Hold it.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
克里斯!
Chris!
特里，我是在里德家打电话。
Terry,I'm calling from Reed's house.
马上派辆车过来。
Send a car out here right away.
里德的妻子被谋杀了。
Reed's wife was murdered.
我告诉你，你不会相信的。
I tell you, you wouldn't believe it.
来吧,Luke。
Come on, Luke.
让杰夫和卡特去里德家附近的黎威路。
Send Jeff and Carter out to the levee road near Reed's house.
Reed!
Luke!
天啊，她血流得很厉害。
Jesus Christ, she's bleeding like crazy.
神。
God.
保持淡定。
Be still.
该死的。
Goddamn it.
很糟糕吧?
It's pretty bad, huh?
我不知道。
I don't know.
你个疯婆子，你怎么了?
You crazy son of a bitch,what's wrong with you?
你疯了吗?
Are you nuts?
你为什么要杀我们?
What are trying to kill us for?
我们什么都没做，伙计!
We haven't done anything, man!
-能帮我拿一下吗?-是的。
- Can you hold that? - Yeah.
你看到了什么?
What do you see?
我什么都没看到，他也不回答。
I don't see anything and he won't answer.
是什么问题?
What's the problem?
点火装置上有一块钢板，我拿不到电线。
There's a steel plate over the ignition and I can't get to the wires.
你的耳朵怎么样了，珍妮?
How's the ear, Jenny?
我想它还在那儿。
It's still there, I think.
她很坚强，不是吗?
She's tough, isn't she?
发生了可怕的事，他认为是我们干的。
Something horrible has happened and he thinks we did it.
嘿!
Hey!
这里有个女孩受伤了，她需要帮助!
We got a girl in here that's hurt and she needs help!
你听到了吗?
Do you hear me?
我们什么都没做!
We haven't done anything!
他会杀了我们的，伙计。
He's gonna kill us, man.
他什么都不在乎。
He doesn't care about anything.
我跟你说，我不喜欢被困在这艘船屋里。
I'll tell you what,I don't like being stuck on this houseboat.
大约50码的地方有个舷外艇。
There's an outboard up here about 50 yards.
如果我能去，启动它  我们至少能到河的另一边。
If I can get to it, get it started we can at least get on the other side of the river.
你要怎么去才不会中枪?
How are you gonna get there without getting shot?
我想我会游泳。
I think I can swim.
你能用这个游泳吗?
Can you swim with this?
不，你留着吧。
No, you keep it.
把它。
Take it.
你一听到那狗娘养的发动，就赶紧出去准备跳进去。
The second you hear that son of a bitch start up, get outside and be ready to jump in.
好吧?
All right?
好吧，我们一会儿见。
All right, I'll see you in a minute.
该死的。
Goddamn.
Reed!
开始，加油，开始。
Start, come on, start.
来吧,克里斯。
Come on, Chris.
韦恩,他为什么会停止?
Wayne,why'd he stop?
克里斯!
Chris!
——克里斯!——克里斯!
- Chris! - Chris!
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
克里斯!
Chris!
克里斯,回答我们!
Chris, answer us!
克里斯?
Chris?
克里斯。
Chris.
克里斯，是你吗?
Chris, is that you?
克里斯?
Chris?
Reed。
Reed.
卢克。
Luke.
一切都会没事的，卢克。
Everything's gonna be okay, Luke.
我对天发誓，一切都会没事的。
I swear to God, everything's gonna be okay.